So while I was in Kenya with One Love Chapel Club, I got the opportunity to visit a school in an underprivileged settlement in Nairobi,
and I offered to pay the school fees for 28 students to go to high school.
Now, in Kenya, you have to pay for school from primary to middle to high school.
And of course, many people do not have that money, but I truly believe that education is the key to our liberation.
And in innumerable cases, education is the key to being able to get out of poverty.
So when I learned that I would be able to afford this, I jumped at the opportunity to do so,
and I'm very proud and honored to be able to help these individuals, 28 of them, to change their lives, their family lives, their legacies, etc.
So when I see comments like this, where someone says, well, we have students here in America, why aren't you helping them?
Well, first of all, I do help them, but I also understand that we have a very different situation here in America than in other places like Kenya.
I also understand that there's a very big difference in someone being able to attend college and someone being able to attend high school.
And for me, the ability to be able to impact 28 lives where in America I may be able to impact like one or two, I'm going to jump at that opportunity.
Then there's this idiot who said, I agree with your perspective and anyone who says different deep down agrees too.
They live in a whole continent where their leader is Black African and yet still they need help.
They are not oppressed at all.
They just face Black corrupted leaders, which I'm sure they could resolve if they woke up.
So yeah, I agree with your perspective.
Okay, okay, okay.
This is giving our ancestors chose slavery.
Folks, the reality is, is that everyone everywhere is having this difficult time.
And if you can help, do so.